Okay, a couple of more accessories for your nurse costume.
The first is bandages and nurses of course are known for giving medical aid and attention and bandages are a nice easy low lying fruit to add to your nurse costume.
How do you do this?
Go out and get party streamers.
White is the best color for this.
It makes an easy bandage.
You can even go around the party or your Halloween gathering and bandage people up throughout the evening.
Simply applying by unrolling it over.
It is nice and resilient.
Yet you can tear it pretty easily as well.
So this is a really nice fun effect to your nurse costume to where you can kind of bring in more of the trapping of a nurse into your party.
Another thing which you can also add for some humor are latex gloves.
These of course are used when nurses want to watch out about germs or other nasties in treating their patients and in not spreading them to others.
It is a sanitary precautionary measure.
So you can of course have these gloves on.
You may get a lot of interesting questions about them, but they are a very fun nurse accessory.